your mother told me that you are doing amazing business in
hotels.
If you can't understand it yourself, then at
least ask. Do
you know who the owner of the hotel
is? That's the
kind of person we are having dinner with today. He is a
very big man and who knows how much
money he gives to him dishonestly that when he is a
blacklisted man and tries to claim his rights,
Vijay, it would be better if you do
n't try to explain all this to me. I
know very well what kind of criminals thrive in such hotels, so there is no
need, it doesn't matter to
me. Vijay, people everywhere will
say that CP sahab's son should have
worked in this coloured hotel. Now I will have to
listen to the rest. Vijay, whether people say it is
wrong or not, that is wrong, so why are you
asking so many times whether you
got a job in such a place or this is some dishonest
business?
Stop this nonsense. If you do
n't feel the difference between law breakers and law protectors, then go and get
your brain treated.
Chetan, listen, what
capability are you talking about with you, that scoundrel has done ordinary work.  It is a very good
job and the situation is such that no one is
ready to listen to a word against him
that hey do some small favor for him tomorrow,
we will be
robbed above all,
Jai Ho,
I am not sorry that you
misbehaved with me, it has happened that
you all are like that, how many hours your cheeks
and tomorrow you will be
passing
which one is
that I am talking about, do not speak in the heat,
call
and if you have got a job there,
yes sir, I am angry with you, you have to do a
job of 26,
pass in this session